{
    "subject": "Alan_Rudolph",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Trixie__film_",
    "human_readable": "Alan Rudolph created the film Trixie.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9239694476127625,
            "question": "What type of work did Alan Rudolph create titled Trixie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.859342634677887,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Alan Rudolph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8077560663223267,
            "question": "What is the title of the film made by Alan Rudolph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7944106459617615,
            "question": "What did Alan Rudolph create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7919411659240723,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Alan Rudolph."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7523900866508484,
            "question": "Who directed the film Trixie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7002200484275818,
            "question": "Is Alan Rudolph known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5845380425453186,
            "question": "Is Alan Rudolph a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5842746496200562,
            "question": "Who is the director of the movie Trixie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48212912678718567,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film directed by Alan Rudolph?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alan Rudolph created the film Trixie.",
            "html": "yago_9748_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the director of the movie Trixie?",
            "html": "yago_9748_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Alan Rudolph a filmmaker?",
            "html": "yago_9748_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Alan Rudolph known for directing films?",
            "html": "yago_9748_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9748_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The key phrases that confirm this are:\n\n* \"Trixie is a 2000 American mystery-crime film directed by Alan Rudolph and starring Emily Watson, Nick Nolte, Will Patton and Brittany Murphy.\"\n* \"Directed and written by Alan Rudolph\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Trixie is a 2000 American mystery-crime film directed by Alan Rudolph and starring Emily Watson, Nick Nolte, Will Patton and Brittany Murphy.\" This information supports the statement that Alan Rudolph created the film Trixie."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}